{
    "en": [
      {"question": "In Germany, Oktoberfest is celebrated with what beverage?", "answer": "Beer"},
      {"question": "What alcoholic beverage are Russians most famous for?", "answer": "Vodka"},
      {"question": "What is the type of beer made from cactus called?", "answer": "Pulque"},
      {"question": "I get wetter the more you dry. What am I?", "answer": "Towel"},
      {"question": "Which sport game was played on the moon?", "answer": "Golf"},
      {"question": "What is the most consumed beverage in the world?", "answer": "Tea"},
      {"question": "Which type of meat is consumed the most in the world?", "answer": "Chicken"},
      {"question": "What is the name of Batman's butler?", "answer": "Alfred"},
      {"question": "What is the most famous Japanese alcoholic beverage?", "answer": "Sake"},
      {"question": "Which country has the highest beer consumption in the world?", "answer": "China"},
      {"question": "What is the smallest country in the world?", "answer": "Vatican"},
      {"question": "How many decimal places does the number pi have?", "answer": "Infinite"}
    ],
    "pt": [
      {"question": "Na Alemanha, Oktoberfest é celebrado com que bebida?", "answer": "Cerveja"},
      {"question": "Os russos mais famosos por qual bebida alcoólica? ", "answer": "Vodka"},
      {"question": "Como se chama o tipo de cerveja feita de cacto?", "answer": "Pulque"},
      {"question": "Fico cada vez mais molhado, quanto mais você seca. O que sou eu?", "answer": "Toalha"},
      {"question": "Qual jogo esportivo foi jogado na lua?", "answer": "Golfe"},
      {"question": "Qual é a bebida mais consumida no mundo?", "answer": "Chá"},
      {"question": "Que tipo de carne as pessoas consomem mais no mundo?", "answer": "Carne de frango"},
      {"question": "Qual é o nome do mordomo do Batman?", "answer": "Alfred"},
      {"question": "Qual é a bebida alcoólica japonesa mais famosa?", "answer": "Sake"},
      {"question": "Qual país tem o maior consumo de cerveja do mundo?", "answer": "China"},
      {"question": "Qual o menor país do mundo?", "answer": " Vaticano"},
      {"question": "Quantas casas decimais tem o número pi?", "answer":"Infinitas"}
    ],
    "es":[
      {"question": "¿En Alemania, con qué bebida se celebra el Oktoberfest?", "answer": "Cerveza"},
      {"question": "¿Por qué bebida alcohólica son más famosos los rusos?", "answer": "Vodka"},
      {"question": "¿Cómo se llama el tipo de cerveza hecha de cactus?", "answer": "Pulque"},
      {"question": "Me vuelvo cada vez más mojado mientras más me secas. ¿Qué soy?", "answer": "Toalla"},
      {"question": "¿Qué deporte se jugó en la luna?", "answer": "Golf"},
      {"question": "¿Cuál es la bebida más consumida en el mundo?", "answer": "Té"},
      {"question": "¿Qué tipo de carne es más consumida en el mundo?", "answer": "Carne de pollo"},
      {"question": "¿Cuál es el nombre del mayordomo de Batman?", "answer": "Alfred"},
      {"question": "¿Cuál es la bebida alcohólica japonesa más famosa?", "answer": "Sake"},
      {"question": "¿Qué país tiene el mayor consumo de cerveza en el mundo?", "answer": "China"},
      {"question": "¿Cuál es el país más pequeño del mundo?", "answer": "Vaticano"},
      {"question": "¿Cuántos decimales tiene el número pi?", "answer":"Infinitos"}
    ]
  }